When it comes to war... America means business
War, Inc. is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Joshua Seftel.
In the future, the desert country of Turaqistan is torn by a riot after private corporation
Tamerlane, owned by the former Vice President of the United States, has taken over.
Brand Hauser, a hitman who suppresses his emotions by gobbling down hot sauce, is
hired by the corporation's head to kill the CEO of their competitors.
Brand Hauser, played by John Cusack.
Yonica Babyyeah, played by Hilary Duff.
Natalie Hegalhuzen, played by Marisa Tomei.
Marsha Dillon, played by Joan Cusack.
Mr. Vice President, played by Dan Aykroyd.
Ooq-Mi-Fay Taqnufmini, played by Sergej Trifunović.
is a 2008 American political action comedy film directed by Joshua
Seftel and starring John Cusack and Hilary Duff.
Cusack also co-wrote and produced the film.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.